

JOCELYN PROCTOR

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

After working for several years in the education sector I recently graduated from Le Wagon, a 9 week Ruby on Rails Full stack Web Development Bootcamp and am now looking for my first employment as a web developer. I am excited to learn new technologies, programming languages, and frameworks. I know how to work in a team and am a good communicator.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Ruby on Rails
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- ES6 Javascript
- React JS
- Relational databases, SQL, Postgres
- APIs, JSON, scraping
- Wireframes, prototyping, UI design
- Git, Github, technical workflow-
- Test driven development

LANGUAGES

- English Native Speaker
- German B2

WORK EXPERIENCE

LE WAGON

Teaching Assistant | 2020 - Present

- provide 1:1 support through video calls to help current students solve problems and reiterate core concepts with them.

OXXYMORON GMBH

Office for Inclusion and Education/ Kita Educator Intern | 2019 - 2020

- Assisted in daily activities and routines at the kita
- Worked in a bilingual kita as well as a German speaking kita
- Worked closely with the Referentin regarding inclusion policies and practices

AMERICAN SCHOOL OF BILBAO

College Advisor/Classroom Educator | 2016-2018

- Implemented a structured university application process for students
- Planned, managed and implemented the science curriculum for year 6
- Incorporated Google Classroom and virtual lab simulations into the curriculum

CONTACT ME



jocelynkproctor@gmail.com https://proctor-webworks.com



+49 1727197959



Spandauer Damm 50 14059 Berlin Germany



https://github.com/jp448



www.linkedin.com/in/jocelynproctor-448448jkp

EDUCATION HISTORY

LE WAGON BERLIN - BATCH 398

UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA AT CHAPEL HILL

Bachelor of Arts in Political Science, Second Major in Economics

- Minor in Women's and Gender Studies
- GPA: 3.44
- Dean's List: 2 Semesters

UNIVERSITY OF NOTTINGHAM Semester Abroad

CEDAR RIDGE HIGH SCHOOL International Baccalaureate Diploma recipient

PERSONAL WEB PROJECTS

https://welcome.proctorwebworks.com

-Welcome is an app that helps expats navigate moving to a new country. It was developed in the last 2 weeks at le wagon

https://bikematch.proctorwebworks.com

- BikeMatch is an app with an Airbnb rental like market, but with bikes

https://mr-cocktail.proctorwebworks.com

- Mr. Cocktail is an app where users can post cocktail recipies